Thank you for watching!
Hallo! Ste. is about to start!
We're going to start the "Halo! Ste. This time we have Akari Emura from Juice-Juice and Shiori Nishida from Beyonce Subway!
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Please bear with us until the end.
And as I announced the other day, I, Akari Emura, will be leaving Hello! Project and Juice-Juice after the spring tour in 2024.
Although there is only a limited amount of time left, I will continue to give it my all and look forward to your continued support.
Project 2023 Summer City Circuit will be held at the Hello! Project 2023 Summer City Circuit will conclude at the Tachikawa Stage Garden on September 2 and 3.
How do you feel about this encore tour? Do you feel that you have evolved?
Yes, Juice-Juice is now performing with the highest number of members in the history of Juice-Juice with the addition of a new member, Miku Kawashima,
I think we have been able to give an even more powerful performance.
We, Beyonce, have been challenging ourselves to perform a cappella in the song "Koshitan Ta Turn",
We have been working hard at every rehearsal, matching the pitch and adjusting the piano, and I think the quality of our performance is improving each time we perform.
Juice-Juice will start Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour 2023 JUICETORY on September 23.
We would like to make this tour a good one-year soaking of the year.
And Beyonce will perform at Thailand Japan Iconic Music Fest 2 023 on September 23.
Congratulations!
We are all very excited about this being our first live performance overseas,
Juice-Juice has done a lot of overseas performances, hasn't she?
We are grateful for that.
I am sure that many people who do not speak Japanese will come to see us,
Do you have any suggestions on how to communicate with them?
I had a local staff member talk to me about everything from pronunciation to the music,
It was like a mini-copy of the whole thing, and we all studied until the very last minute before the show,
But when we had to MC after the show, things didn't go as well as we had practiced,
But even though I was speaking in Japanese, everyone understood me.
Even those who didn't understand me reacted in a way that they enjoyed the show,
They were really kind-hearted people, so I think I was saved by that.
So, I will try my best to enjoy the show with a little peace of mind.
I want to have fun.
Yes, I will. I will do my best. I will enjoy it.
Now, please watch this video.
Here you go!
This is the first performance by all 14 members.
This will be the first performance for the 17th term members, so please make sure you all get a good look at it.
Please listen to it. Today's first performance.
Nansan Show! Souzan Show!What a show! Souzan show!
me
You said you were going out.
And then you don't go out
You say you're going out, but you don't go out
You're late getting ready
You keep saying things you can't say
When you eat, you're ugly
I'm a city dweller
Rumble, clatter and dot
I'm so flustered
I know, I know.
I already apologized to your mother.
It's a mess.
You know, I don't know what the future holds.
Look, it's over without me.
Not without me.
You're a man of your word.
That's a lie.
I'm sure I'll regret this, too.
You know, I'm drunk on myself, too.
I'm spoiled, I'm spoiled, I'm spoiled.
I'm the perfect person
Wow Wow Yeah Yeah Yeah
I'm mad at the big family
You're the one who wants to be here
Always you guys
I'm pretty excited.
I'm gonna write you a note.
I know, right?
I knew you'd come.
I knew you'd be here.
I set a time for you to meet me in front of the station.
I should've waited.
Still, I just clicked.
I'm looking at the menu.
I'm looking at them.I'm looking at them.
But they all look...
They all look so good.
I'm staring at them
Wow, if this is the only thing
If this is the only thing that's not going to work...
I won't tolerate it.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
I don't care if you make me say it, it'll fall apart.
I can't do it, I can't do it.
I'm ashamed to admit that I know.
Somehow...
It's more than just a sexual thing
Hey, I'm falling apart at my own size
I'm gonna be like...
I've got to share it with you
Wow Wow Yeah Yeah Yeah
I didn't know you were watching the world.
I'm sorry.
You can leave it there.
I want to make sure the cake is done right.
Please make it quick.
I know, right?
I don't know what the future holds.
You know, without me, you'd be finished.
You're a piece of poo, you're a man.
What's that supposed to mean?
This can be another one of your regrets, Neunika.
You know, I'm drunk on myself too.
I'm a natural at being sweet
Wow, wow, yeah, yeah
The world's a closed book
I've always opened the door when I'm ready
You know, I'm pretty excited about it.
We're going out.
Isn't that right?
The release event at the Ikebukuro Sunshine City Fountain Plaza has ended.The release event at Ikebukuro Sunshine City Fountain Plaza has ended.
No, thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
This was the first event for Haruka Ione and Toako Yumiki from the 17th term, and their first performance.
I was nervous because it was my first performance and the first time to perform a song,
But I really enjoyed it,
I was really surprised to see so many people in the audience, both in the back and in the top rows.
I was so happy.
How was it for you, Ako-chan?
It was my first time to hold a microphone and wear a proper costume,
It was the first time for me to hold a microphone, wear a proper costume, and dance quite violently,
And in front of the audience, I felt that I had become a great idol,
I really felt that I had become an idol in front of the audience.
That's for sure. It was a different kind of tension from the self-introduction.
I think we were also nervous, but we did our best with smiles on our faces.
I think it's good to be at the first performance of 14 wonderful people.
And on this delivery day, the new album Morning Musume。 15 Best Selection THE 25th Anniversary.
Now that it has been released, does anyone have any recommendations for the album?
Yes, I do.
Okay, Oda.
First of all, I'd like to talk about the songs that Seung-guk-san has selected,
I think this is what Morning Musume。 I think this is what Morning Musume。
And there are new songs as well,
There are also new songs, so there is a wide range of songs that include members from the flexible term,
There are also new songs with a wide range of members, so there are a lot of things to listen to.
Yes. Anyone else?
Yes, I do.
Oh, yeah.
We recorded two or three versions of the song, and everyone silecasted,
There is a line in the second verse of "Happy Summer Wedding.
I had to play the second verse once as a test, but that was all I had ever done,
The song is there, so please listen to it.
Also, there are 12 of us in Stearistomic,
I had a lot of fun doing that,
I hope you will pay attention to that as well.
This album is filled with a lot of feelings.This album is filled with a lot of feelings.
So, Morning Musume。 Best Selection THE 25th Anniversary
Please listen to it a lot. Thank you very much.
That's all for Morning Musume。 15.
Thank you very much.
Are you having fun? Watch the rest of the show!
Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice, Beyonce, and Shiori Nishida of Subway, presenting Halo! Stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo!
Yes, I'll do my best.
Beyonce celebrates 40 years of major label debut this month.
Major Debut Beyonce
What is the best word to describe Shiori Nishida today?
Voice in love
Her second photo book, 20-year-old Shiori, was released last week.
Please introduce this work in your own words.
Twenty years old indeed!
What has made you smile recently?
When I saw the success of the members.
Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year
What song do you like to listen to at the end of summer?
Summer Reggae Rainbow
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
So, let me ask you this.
First of all, I would like to ask you a question.
What made you smile? I'd like to ask you this question.
When I saw the success of our members.
Yes, that's right.
Honoka Kobayashi was playing the piano in a TV program called "Teppo
I saw her playing piano on TV.
I was very moved to see Honoka Kobayashi working so hard
I was very moved by her effort.
The chat in the members' group was very active.
Every time Honoka Kobayashi appeared on the stage
Every time Honoka Kobayashi appeared on the stage, they would say "Wow, she's so cute" or "Every time she finished her performance, she looked so nice.
Every time Honoka Kobayashi appeared on the stage.And so on and so forth.
It was heartwarming to hear that the members were sending each other
It made my heart warm.
I felt that the members of the group are a good group.
They support each other every day, don't they?
That's right.
And you know what?
Last week, the second photo book
Hatachi no shiori (bookmark for hatachi) was released!
I was asked to introduce this work in my own words.
I'm just a teenager.
I'm really "Hachitaro"!
This book is different from the last one in that it has a more mature feel, but at the same time
It has a mature look, but at the same time
I was taken in a way that is uniquely me.
I was also photographed in a cute way that is uniquely me.
I hope you will enjoy seeing me at my age.
We'll be back with more questions for Ms. Uemura after the VTR.
Hello! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10
Topinoleitmairaishu It doesn't matter what you call me.
Each one has its own Subaki Factory, Yuuki! It's My Life September 27 On Missile
Is it the summer, is it a dream, is it a little emotional instability, whose fault is it?
Stetoshina Lomber Kinryu Single Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer on sale now!
Tea Horse
Shake Nare
I can't choose between TV and screams
Pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka
Ochanoma New single Yoridorimidori on sale now!
Hallo! Halo!
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Uemura some questions.
I'll do my best.
Who do you think has changed the role of Juice-Juice since it became an 11-member group?
I am in the middle of the 10th anniversary year of Juice-Juice.
When we held an event on the day of the founding of the group When you graduate from Juice-Juice next spring, what do you want to do with the members before your graduation?
Laugh a lot What was the most popular gourmet food for Uemura this summer?
Tomato-flavored pickled plums What is today's fashion?
Today's fashion is, as I am announcing my graduation once again.Today's fashion is, as I'm announcing my graduation once again.
I usually wear mainly monotone or black, but I wore this with flowers in mind.
Thank you very much. It's beautiful.
Thank you. You wore a floral print today, too.
It made me happy. It made me happy. It's true.
The 11 members who left the company changed their roles.
I made it my own, but yes, it's changing every time, but also...
There are many points where I myself really feel that things have been changing since the announcement of my graduation.
I really feel that it has changed a lot since the announcement of my graduation, so I have decided to do this.
It's wonderful. And what do you want to do before you graduate from Juice-Juice?
Yes, I want to laugh a lot. I thought it was wonderful when you said you wanted to laugh.
Thank you very much. I don't have a specific thing I want to do.
I don't have a specific thing I want to do or anything, I just like to laugh.
I can't smile twice because my old photos have disappeared.
I can't smile twice, so I'd like to keep the memories of the members on my cell phone or something while I still can.
Yes, I think it's very nice. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. We will continue after this.
This is Natsuyaki Masashi. I'm Kamura Eid of Angulum.
I'm looking forward to seeing it finished.
Now, what will you make this time?
Yes, here it is today.
Oh!
What?
Here we go!
Wow!
Bonito.
Bonito!
I had it cut up and made into nigiri-zushi (sushi ball).
Bonito nigiri!
Yes, I would like to.
It's the best!
I look forward to working with you.
Wow, this is the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
This place is quite important.
Yes, I've already gone to the head.
It went.
That's great.It's amazing.
The meat is still very fragile.
Gentle.
With a bedding.
So, where do we start this time?
Yes, I would like to start searing the bonito.
Well, I just took this out of the refrigerator,
The salt is nice,
It's nice, the teriyaki.
It's very nice. It's very shiny,
But it won't burn if it has water in it,
So, I have to remove the water from the refrigerator,
But you have to be careful because it sticks easily.
The bonito is a bit sticky.
Now, let's start the actual searing process,
The skin is the main part.
The flesh should be just lightly colored.
Yes.
Fire!
Especially at first, if you cook it too quickly, it will be too tight.
That's good.
Oh!
Good, good, good.
Wow! The skin is crackling!
The char on this side is so good.
That's good. It's nicely charred.
When you grill it like this, the aroma of the burnt skin goes well with it.
Isn't it good?
I like this way of grilling.
If you cut it in this state, it will easily fall apart because it is so hot,
I'll close it in the refrigerator.
Yes, I understand.
Tightly and firmly.
Put it in the refrigerator.
Put it in the refrigerator.Place in the refrigerator.
Then make the rice.
Sushi is already made with the fry I made to imitate the meat,
There was too much tuna meat when I was practicing the dismantling of tuna,
We made several pieces of sushi and ate them.
It's amazing.
Then already.
It's my original.
It's like an original rice ball,
I'm glad that I was able to learn it musically this time.
I'm not a professional teacher either,
I've been serving sushi to my family at home,
It's been more than 10 years now.
It's amazing.
It also says 2 tablespoons, plus 2 teaspoons.
Roughly 40 ml or so.
Two tablespoons of sugar.
2 teaspoons of salt, too.
It's dissolved.
Then here's the key,
First of all, remove a little bit of the rough heat.
It's like loosening it up a little bit.
The water content is very low, so you have to go all the way through.
Then, go to the next step.
Yes. Then, mix while cutting.
Mix while cutting.
Yes, stop once.
Yes.
Here,
Let it cool.
Flap.
Yes.
Yes. And mix again.
Mix.
This is something like this, often at the same time,
I mean, mother lathers and father mixes at the same time, or something like that,There's something about the mother foaming and the father mixing, or something like that,
I heard that it's better if there are no bubbles when mixing.
I see.
I guess you can pick this up a little bit.
Oh, huh,
Taste it.
Can I taste it?
Go ahead.
Yay!
And, you know, touch it with your right hand,
I think it's still sticky.
Oh, wow.
I'm sure your hands will stick together.
It will stick to your hand.
Can I eat it?
Please do.
Bon appétit.
Taste it.
Mmm.
Is it good?
It's good.
I do.
Not too sweet.
Mmm.
Sorry, the firmness is just right.
Just right.
It was delicious.
Yes.
Okay, now it's time to cut the sushi, not the sashimi.
Please do.
For sashimi, you cut it like this on the skin.
But for sushi, the skin is on the bottom, right?In sushi, the skin is on the bottom.
The skin is on the bottom and the mountain is on the other side.
The seared condition is just right.
It's just right.
It's seared like this.
It looks like tuna, right?
That's for sure.
Now I'd like to nigiri it.
Please do.
Wash your hands well.
Just the right amount of moisture.
Just like a sushi chef.
Welcome.
You can do it right there.
Come on in.
Enjoy.
Thank you, sushi chef.
How much and how many grams?
Half of that.
Half of this.
It's less than I thought it would be.
Fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy.
Even if you're good at it, you're good at it.
Corocororo means corocororo
Hold the stuff.
Over here on the left hand side.
Put the rice on this side.
Put the rice on top.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Muni nya.
Hold this.
Give it back already.
Thumbs are important.
Yes, it is.
This thumb is very important.
Right here.This one.
Not bad.
The teacher is very light.
He's doing it so lightly.
It's not that easy.
I thought it was easy.
It's in your hand.
It's not easy.
It's hard to make a shape.
It's hard.
That's great, that's great, that's great
That's great!
Nice, nice, nice, nice!
It's like a cologne.
Oh, well...
Tap, tap, tap.
Come on, baby.
Do it again.
One more time.
Put it in.
Roll it up.
Then put the rice on top.
Yes, sir.
Oh, no!
It's just like it looks.
Like this.
Yes, sir.
Thumb.
Click.
Cupped from the side too.
There you go.
Turn over
From the top with
Press
Yes, sir.
A technique? What kind of technique is that?
Quick.early termination (e.g. of a contract)
I don't know about this, but if you cut into it...
If you cut into it, it's definitely balanced.
It's warped... but still...
It's amazing how quickly it's growing.
Advanced
I've never seen that before.
It's so beautiful.
Not bad at all.
But you can tell that you're getting better and better at this as you go along.
You can tell you're getting better at it.
Yes.
The ginger hasn't been used for a long time, right?
That's right.
You can handle it.
And put some green onions on top.
Bon appétit!
It's done!
Hold your hand!
The bonito nigirizushi is ready!
Yay!
How do you like it?
Wow, it was my first time to make a real nigirizushi like this
I'm so glad I learned from the teacher.
I'm so glad I learned from my teacher!
Now, let's look at this bonito nigirizushi that I worked so hard on!
Here it is!
Let's eat it right away!
Bon appétit!
Here you go!
Yum!
Mmm!
Looks delicious!
You worked so hard!
I've never had sushi with pork cutlets before.
I've never had it as sushi before.
It's fun to taste the different flavors of sushi.And when it comes to sushi, it's fun to taste all kinds of flavors.
This grilled meat has a nice flavor too!
It's so good!
By the way, the teacher changed the taste this time.
Instead of soy sauce, I brought persimmon soy sauce.
It tastes even better with sesame oil!
Sesame oil?
I'll give it a try.
If you put too much, it'll be too toxic.
Just a little bit.
And garlic. I just took it down.
Oh, yeah, and garlic, too. You took it down.
It has more punch.
I think that's enough.
Yes, and some sesame oil.
Put some garlic in it.
A little bit.
Mix it in.
Wow, I've never tried sesame oil before.
Yes, it's true.
I knew you made it for me.
Bon appétit!
Yum! Delicious!
Delicious!
Sesame oil is good!
There is no more taste.
It goes great with this. Delicious!
But today, Ayano-chan did all the work herself, from the slicing of the fish, did you enjoy it?
It was a lot of fun!
How was Hello Kitchen?
Hello Kitchen was a lot of fun, and the teacher taught us a lot of things. I learned a lot from the instructor, including how to arrange the dishes, and most of all, Natsuyaki's reaction was great.
Really? Are you sure?
When she was cleaning the fish, she looked so cute when she was backing away from me.
That was scary.
It was the first time for me to see her that close. But I wanted to see Ayano-san cooking, so I was very happy today.
Thank you very much.
So this Hello Kitchen was a lot of fun.So this Hello Kitchen was a lot of fun.
That's all for Hello Kitchen.
Bye bye!
Wow, that looked delicious!
Yes, Uemura-san, how is the cooking situation these days?
Yes, I would like to recommend a dish I made, avocado tempura.
Avocado and tempura is a combination that is not so familiar to many people.
I think it's like that.
The texture is different from that of vegetables or meat, and the tempura is quite thick.
I thought that avocado is very versatile.
I hope you will try to make this dish.
Yes, I, Nishida, recently made a fat-burning soup full of vegetables.
Is it warming?
Yes, it is very warming.
It also burns fat, and you drink it every day.
I make fat-burning soup when I want to lose weight.
I make fat-burning soup when I want to lose weight, but then I have to drink the same soup day after day after day.
So I made a tomato flavor and a salt flavor so that I wouldn't get bored of it, and drank it every day.
Delicious!
Yes, sir!
Halo! Ste!
With Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice,
Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice and Shiori Nishida of Beyonds Subway present "Halo! Ste.
This year, 2023, marks the 25th anniversary of Hello! Project will celebrate its 25th anniversary in 2023.
On September 9 and 10, Hello! Project 25th Anniversary Concert,
Project 25th Anniversary Concert will be held on September 9 and 10, at the first gymnasium of the Ryugu Stadium.
I, Uemura, am the same age as Hello! Project and I am the same age,
Project for my life. Project has a long history,
I am really happy to be a part of that history,
I hope to enjoy this live performance.
There are many attractive senior members who will be performing,
In honor of the 25th anniversary of Hello! Project's 25th anniversary,
Project's 25th anniversary, we would like to share with you some of our favorites from the 25 years of live performances.
I, Uemura, will introduce ℃-ute's last concert in Saitama Super Arena.
This is the final call from the 3rd level team ℃-ute.From the 3rd level team ℃-ute, this is Final Squall.
I like this song so much that I have watched the music video many times,
I think the strength of this song is that they sing positive lyrics in their live performance,
I saw some of the members holding back tears or bursting into tears,
I chose this song because it really moved me a lot.
This song is the first lyric that I sang,
I can't see the world without you, under the flowers, like a branch, about to fall
Goodbye, just keep falling like a branch under a flower
Final squall, like I can write out my loneliness
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I'll scream, I'll scream, I'll scream, I'll scream, I'll scream, I'll scream, I'll scream, I'll scream forever and ever and ever.
Hallo! Sta.
The song I chose is I need you from Momoko Tsugunaga, Last Live, Arigatou, Oketsukenohi.
This is a piano arrangement, or rather, a video of Ms. Tsugunaga singing alone with a piano player,
The lyrics were so beautiful, and the video was so easy to listen to that I felt it was the last live,
The lyrics were so beautiful, and the song was so beautiful that it made me feel like it was really her last live,
It made me think, "I want to be an idol like this.
I don't like to say good-bye.
I only like the words "see you again
Even though we'll never see each other again
It's impossible to forget
You even made me a memory
20I only liked you out of the blue
I wouldn't have liked you all of a sudden
I need you
I'm not very good at this.
I'm sorry I scolded you
I'm sorry I didn't tell you everything.
Hello! Ste!
Hello! Ste.
Who's Shekinda?
Shekinda... Shekinda...
Oh, my God, Mr. White, not again.
A little mistake, a little temper tantrum, a little thunder...
What do you mean? It happens all the time.
How about... wake up, Cheaparee 321.
With a mysterious beatIt's a strange beat.
I haven't even told my parents yet
I'm in the mood to see you again, Suttezu Earth
Don't worry, if it's with you
Shake it up, the future no one knows
With my hands, I'll open up our future
Let's do it with our hearts racing Just
Shake it up!
Shake it up Power to believe in myself
It's ordinary, but it's ordinary.
Here's your chance, see you tomorrow
Darling up and down
Shake it up Shake it!
Shake it up Shake it up
Shake it up Shake shake Shake it move me
Shake it!
Hoo Hoo
Sing it!
Everybody!
It's me and Wonky
Any bhatti, any bhatti, any bhatti, any bhatti, any bhatti
I got plenty of mech pop to go with it
Let's get you in there, smarty pants
I'm gonna jump in here with all my anger, bad, bad, bad
Hey you baby, you're getting high, you're getting stupid
Skelaleskelareskelareskelareskelares
Skelaleskelareskelareskelaree
Oh, it's the order of the miracle
I can't believe I'm gonna lose more
Expectations are so high, I'm so proud of myself
Gently, now, pull it together
Shake it up!
Everybody's got their own
Life goes on, win or lose
Life goes on, life goes on
No matter what time of year it isWhatever the occasion.
I like this.
Shake it around!
Shake it up!
Something that will be created
If it's irreplaceable and infinite
Don't let yourself miss out anymore
Put your hands up!
You can't say you like me
Don't say you love me
Shake it around!
DON DON DON DON DON DON DON DON DON DON DON DON DON
That's the signal
Dance hall
Don't forget about it, don't forget about it
Say!
Shake it around!
Shake it up!
The future that no one knows
Our future we'll pick up with our own hands
Let's see what's in store for us
Hop-step, hop-step Shake it up!
Shake it up!
The power of self-belief
I'm ordinary, but I'm stubborn.
Here's your chance.
My Turn it up and dance!
Shake it lucky nally
Shake it up and dance
Shake it!
Don't say you like it.
Shake it up!
I like you. Shake it nally.I like Shake it nally
Wow!
Together, together!
Woo!
I like it.
Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice and Shiori Nishida of Beyonce Subway present Halo! It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
PROJECT 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT is now underway.
We have only the Tachikawa Stage Garden on September 2 and 3 to go.
We really had a lot of fun memories in this tour, and we would like to run through it until the end.
Juice-Juice will also be going on an autumn tour starting September 23.
We are a group that really loves to perform live, so it is a great blessing to be able to do so many solo tours like this.
Beyonce will be performing overseas for the first time at the Thailand Japan Iconic Music Festival 023 on September 23.
I am very excited and looking forward to it, so I will do my best with all my energy.
And on September 30, Juice-Juice and Beyonce will be performing at the Kyoto Meigetsu Concert 2023 Heian Jingu Gekijo Tsukiyo.
It is a very nice venue, and since I am from Kyoto and Juice-Juice has two members who are from Kyoto, I will enjoy it.
Juice-Juice will be performing at Fruit Zipper x Juice-Juice Fruit Juice on November 23rd.
This is going to be a really wonderful collaboration, and I am sure it will be a great day, so I will do my best.
Beyonce will be performing at NeoBioat Budokan and Biophonic on November 15.
It was a wonderful performance, so please check it out.
Project 25th Anniversary Concert will be held on Saturday, September 9 and Sunday, September 10.
Project's history and the current junior members, so I hope you are looking forward to the special live performance.
Project's history and the current juniors. Project members will appear on the channel.
Project members. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time, I was joined by Akari Emura of Juice-Juice and Sayuri Nishida of Beyonce Subway.
Goodbye~.
Thank you for watching.